A Guide to the Commonwealth Fund records, Grants, SG 1, Series 18 FA290
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Grants, 1979-2003 1987-2003; 4; 53.15 Cubic Feet microfilm reels representing 205 cubic feet of paper records.
  - Community Resource Exchange - #94-67, 1994 (Reel 102, Frame 201)
    Fran Barrett
  - Community Resource Exchange - #9721, 1996 (Reel 102, Frame 323)
  - Community Service Society of New York - #95523, 1995 (Reel 102, Frame 667)
    David Jones
  - Community Service Society of New York - #970357, 1997 (Reel 102, Frame 699)
    Christine Molnar
  - Community Service Society of New York - #980511, Tabs 1-2, 1998 (Reel 102, Frame 896)
  - Community Service Society of New York - #980511, Tabs 3-10, 1998 (Reel 103, Frame 1)
  - Conference Board - #91-43, Tabs 1-9, 1990 (Reel 103, Frame 379)
    Preston Townley
  - Conference Board - #91-43, Tab 10, 1990 (Reel 104, Frame 1)
  - Conservancy for Historic Battery Park - #970933, 1997 (Reel 105, Frame 1)
    Warrie Price
  - Consumers Union of United States, Inc. - #20010397 (Reel 105, Frame 103)
    Trudy Lieberman
  - Consumers Union of United States, Inc. - #96513, 1996 (Reel 105, Frame 371)
    Judith Bell
  - Consumers Union of United States, Inc. - #96528, Tabs 1-3, 1996 (Reel 106, Frame 1)
  - Consumers Union of United States, Inc. - #96528, Tabs 4-10, 1996 (Reel 107, Frame 1)
  - Consumers Union of United States, Inc. - #970594, 1997 (Reel 107, Frame 156)
  - Consumers Union of United States, Inc. - #980444, 1998 (Reel 108, Frame 1)
  - Cooke Foundation for Special Education - #95116, 1994 (Reel 108, Frame 782)
    Karen Robards
  - Coordinated Care Management - #10019, 1987 (Reel 108, Frame 857)
    MaryAnn Bolles
  - Coordinated Care Management - #10825, 1988 (Reel 109, Frame 1)
    Gloria Brennan
  - Copiah Lincoln Community College - #91-26, 1990 (Reel 109, Frame 64)
    Howell Garner
  - Cornell University - #990420, 1998 (Reel 109, Frame 596)
    Mark Callahan
  - Cornell University Medical College - #93-53, 1995 (Reel 109, Frame 745)
    John Dusseau
  - Cornell University Medical College - #94-72, 1994 (Reel 109, Frame 793)
    David Rogers
  - Corporation for Supportive Housing - #92-68, Tabs 1-2, 1991 (Reel 109, Frame 847)
    Julie Sandorf
  - Corporation for Supportive Housing - #92-68, Tabs 3-10, 1991 (Reel 110, Frame 1)
  - Council for Jewish Elderly - #10020, 1986 (Reel 110, Frame 337)
    Daniel Silverstein
  - Council on Foundations - #10445, 1987 (Reel 111, Frame 1)
    James Joseph
  - Council on Foundations - #11164, 1989 (Reel 111, Frame 161)
  - Council on Foundations - #2000487 (Reel 111, Frame 447)
    Dorothy Ridings
  - Council on Foundations - #20010342 (Reel 111, Frame 646)
  - Council on Foundations - #20020512, 2001 (Reel 111, Frame 938)
  - Council on Foundations - #8746, 1986 (Reel 112, Frame 1)
  - Council on Foundations - #90-49, 1990 (Reel 112, Frame 315)
  - Council on Foundations - #91-72, 1991 (Reel 112, Frame 663)
  - Council on Foundations - #92-55, 1992 (Reel 112, Frame 945)
    Kate Guedj
  - Council on Foundations - #93-61, 1993 (Reel 113, Frame 1)
  - Council on Foundations - #94-96, 1994 (Reel 113, Frame 447)
  - Council on Foundations - #95-85, 1995 (Reel 114, Frame 1)
  - Council on Foundations - #98-78, 1996 (Reel 114, Frame 229)
  - Council on Foundations - #96643, 1997 (Reel 114, Frame 410)
  - Council on Foundations - #970634, 1998 (Reel 114, Frame 660)
  - Council on Foundations - #980478, 1998 (Reel 114, Frame 779)
  - Council on Foundations - #980530, 1998 (Reel 114, Frame 905)
  - Council on Foundations - #990408, 1999 (Reel 115, Frame 1)
  - Dartmouth College - #80-13, 1982 (Reel 115, Frame 250)
    Henry Harbury
  - Dartmouth College - #94-11, Tabs 1-2, 1993 (Reel 115, Frame 948)
    Ann Flood
  - Dartmouth College - #94-11, Tabs 3-10, 1993 (Reel 116, Frame 1)
  - Dartmouth College - #96909, 1996 (Reel 116, Frame 366)
    John Wasson
  - Dartmouth College Medical School - #96260, 1996 (Reel 116, Frame 538)
    Allen Dietrich
  - Datastat, Inc. - #95-37, Tabs 1-9, 1994 (Reel 116, Frame 761)
    Sherry Marcy
  - Datastat, Inc. - #95-37, Tab 10, 1994 (Reel 117, Frame 1)
  - Datastat, Inc. - #96766, 1996 (Reel 117, Frame 1010)
  - Datastat, Inc. - #970591, 1997 (Reel 118, Frame 1)
    Lou Magilavy
  - Delmarva Foundation for Medical Care - #20020708 (Reel 118, Frame 316)
    Virginia Paganelli
  - Denver MetroNet - #10840, 1986 (Reel 118, Frame 552)
    Donald Hoagland
  - Denver Museum of Natural History - #90-45, 1990 (Reel 118, Frame 799)
    James Goddard
  - Design Trust for Public Space - #980280, 1998 (Reel 118, Frame 985)
    Andrea Woodner
  - Dole Foundation - #9041, 1990 (Reel 119, Frame 1)
    Carl Rush
  - Duke University - #20000364 (Reel 119, Frame 101)
    Ralph Snyderman
  - Duke University - #90-46, 1989 (Reel 119, Frame 209)
    William Anlyan
  - Duke University - #91-59, 1990 (Reel 119, Frame 346)
    Robert Wright
  - Duke University - #94-35, 1993 (Reel 119, Frame 430)
    Mark Charles Rogers
  - Duke University - #96031, 1995 (Reel 119, Frame 579)
    Warren Herndon
  - Duke University Medical Center - #96911, 1995 (Reel 119, Frame 626)
  - Economic and Social Research Institute - #2000441 (Reel 119, Frame 683)
    Jack Meyer
  - Education and Research Foundation of the Better Business Bureau of New York - #970323, 1996 (Reel 119, Frame 784)
    B. Opotowsky
  - Education and Research Fund of EBRI - #20000355, 1999 (Reel 120, Frame 1)
    Paul Fronstin
  - Education and Research Fund of EBRI - #20000645 (Reel 120, Frame 70)
  - Education and Research Fund of EBRI - #20010414 (Reel 120, Frame 317)
  - Education Development Center - #96255, 1995 (Reel 120, Frame 436)
    Stu Cohen
  - Educational Film Center - #11159, 1988 (Reel 120, Frame 696)
    Robert Gardner
  - Eleanor Roosevelt Monument Fund - #95-73, 1994 (Reel 120, Frame 889)
    Franklin D. Roosevelt III
  - Elliott White Springs Memorial Hospital - #91-66, 1991 (Reel 120, Frame 981)
    Ann Nelson
  - Elmhurst Hospital Center - #94-36, 1993 (Reel 121, Frame 1)
    Brenda LaVann
  - Emory University - #95451, Tabs 1-2 (February 14, 1996), 1994 (Reel 121, Frame 203)
    Carol Hogue
  - Emory University - #95451, Tab 3 (June 9-11, 1996), 1994 (Reel 122, Frame 1)
  - Emory University - #95451, Tabs 3-9 (April 22, 1996), 1994 (Reel 123, Frame 1)
  - Emory University - #95451, Tab 10, 1994 (Reel 124, Frame 1)
  - Emory University - #980842, 1998 (Reel 124, Frame 456)
    Dale Nordenberg
  - Emory University - #990913, 1999 (Reel 124, Frame 555)
    Kenneth Thorpe
  - Employee Benefit Research Institute - #11181, 1989 (Reel 124, Frame 677)
    William Cusler
  - Employee Benefit Research Institute - #20020335 (Reel 124, Frame 1127)
  - Employee Benefit Research Institute - #20020464 (Reel 125, Frame 1)
  - Employee Benefit Research Institute - #980209, 1998 (Reel 125, Frame 231)
    Dallas Salisbury
  - Employee Benefit Research Institute - #990082, 1999 (Reel 125, Frame 291)
  - Enterprise Foundation - #93-11, 1992 (Reel 125, Frame 400)
    William Frey
  - Executive Office of Public Safety - #10392, 1987 (Reel 125, Frame 792)
    Terrance Schiavone
  - Executive Office of Public Safety - #10426, 1987 (Reel 125, Frame 1080)
  - Executive Office of Public Safety - #10451, 1988 (Reel 126, Frame 1)
  - Executive Office of Public Safety - #90-07, Tabs 1-8, 1989 (Reel 126, Frame 679)
  - Executive Office of Public Safety - #90-07, Tabs 9-10, 1989 (Reel 127, Frame 1)
  - Executive Office of Public Safety - #91-11, 1990 (Reel 127, Frame 203)
  - Exploratorium - #8494, 1984 (Reel 127, Frame 553)
    Frank Oppenheimer
  - FACCT, Inc. - #20000252, 1999 (Reel 127, Frame 718)
    Christina Bethell
  - FACCT, Inc. - #20000512 (Reel 127, Frame 850)
  - FACCT, Inc. - #20010529 (Reel 127, Frame 1010)
    David Lansky
  - FACCT, Inc. - #980495, 1997 (Reel 128, Frame 1)
  - FACCT, Inc. - #980498, 1998 (Reel 128, Frame 211)
  - Families and Work Institute - #91-81, 1991 (Reel 129, Frame 1)
    Ellen Galinsky
  - Families and Work Institute - #94-136, 1994 (Reel 130, Frame 1)
  - Families and Work Institute - #95099, 1995 (Reel 130, Frame 294)
  - Families and Work Institute - #95457, 1995 (Reel 131, Frame 1)
  - Families and Work Institute - #96677, 1996 (Reel 131, Frame 180)
  - Families and Work Institute - #97119, 1997 (Reel 131, Frame 516)
  - Families and Work Institute - #990044, 1999 (Reel 131, Frame 734)
  - Families USA Foundation - #970442, 1997 (Reel 132, Frame 1, Folder 1)
    Geraldine Dallek
  - Families USA Foundation - #971068, 1997 (Reel 132, Frame 136)
  - Floating Hospital - #92-26, 1991 (Reel 132, Frame 383)
    Mary Bleiberg
  - Foundation Center - #10804, 1986 (Reel 132, Frame 565)
    Thomas Buckman
  - Foundation Center - #11220, Tabs 1-9, 1988 (Reel 132, Frame 826)
    Wilhelm Bartenbach
  - Foundation Center - #11220, Tab 10, 1988 (Reel 133, Frame 1)
  - Foundation Center - #91-78, 1991 (Reel 133, Frame 536)
    Sara Engelhardt
  - Foundation Center - #94-94, 1994 (Reel 133, Frame 925)
  - Foundation Center - #970636, 1997 (Reel 134, Frame 1)
  - Foundation Center - #980569, 1998 (Reel 134, Frame 106)
    Sara Englehardt
  - Foundation Center - #9902, 1998 (Reel 134, Frame 264)
  - Foundation Center - #990510, 1999 (Reel 134, Frame 389)
  - Foundation for Health Services Research - #10491, 1987 (Reel 134, Frame 480)
  - Foundation for Health Services Research - #10703, 1989 (Reel 134, Frame 539)
  - Foundation for Health Services Research - #92-44, 1991 (Reel 135, Frame 1)
  - Foundation for Health Services Research - #94-19, 1993 (Reel 135, Frame 274)
  - Foundation for Health Services Research - #95-12, Tabs 1-2, 1994 (Reel 135, Frame 815)
  - Foundation for Health Services Research - #95-12, Tabs 3-10, 1994 (Reel 136, Frame 1)
  - Foundation for Health Services Research - #96002, 1996 (Reel 137, Frame 1)
  - Foundation for Healthcare Policy and Evaluation - #20010381 (Reel 137, Frame 450)
    Sheila Leatherman
  - Foundation for Healthcare Policy and Evaluation - #990771, Tabs 1-5, 1999 (Reel 137, Frame 566)
    Patricia Venus
  - Foundation for Healthcare Policy and Evaluation - #990771, Tabs 6-10, 1999 (Reel 138, Frame 1)
  - Foundation for International Studies on Social Security - #20020031 (Reel 138, Frame 541)
    Han Emanuel
  - Foundation for the National Capitol Region - #95473, 1995 (Reel 138, Frame 601)
    Leon Dash
  - Freedom Institute - #111045, 1987 (Reel 138, Frame 763)
    Edmona Mansell
  - Freedom Institute - #8873, 1988 (Reel 138, Frame 850)
  - Freedom Institute - #90-13, 1989 (Reel 138, Frame 915)
    Elinor McClaren
  - Freedom Institute - #91-02, 1990 (Reel 138, Frame 962)
  - Freedom Institute - #92-02, 1991 (Reel 138, Frame 1008)
  - Freedom Institute - #93-13, 1992 (Reel 138, Frame 1078)
    Cary Normile
  - Freedom Institute - #94-03, 1993 (Reel 138, Frame 1139)
  - Freedom Institute - #9720, 1996 (Reel 139, Frame 1)
  - Freedom Institute - #9887, 1998 (Reel 139, Frame 64)
    Cathleen Clements
  - French American Foundation - #95575, 1995 (Reel 139, Frame 117)
    Susan Watts
  - Fresh Air Fund - #11046, 1987 (Reel 139, Frame 634)
    Jenny Morgenthau
  - Fresh Air Fund - #8874, 1988 (Reel 139, Frame 722)
  - Fresh Air Fund - #91-03, 1989 (Reel 139, Frame 879)
  - Fresh Air Fund - #90-14, 1990 (Reel 139, Frame 914)
  - Fresh Air Fund - #94-78, 1994 (Reel 139, Frame 945)
    Lisa Watson
  - Fresh Air Fund - #9714, 1996 (Reel 140, Frame 1)
  - Fresh Air Fund - #9888, 1998 (Reel 140, Frame 73)
  - Friends and Relatives of the Institutionalized Aged - #11089, 1987 (Reel 140, Frame 139)
    Cynthia Rudder
  - Friends of Harlem Hospital - #95-31, 1994 (Reel 140, Frame 520)
    Pamela Hamilton
  - Friends of Sheba Medical Center - #980944, 1998 (Reel 140, Frame 549)
    Tel Hashomer
  - Fund for Aging Services - #92-72, 1992 (Reel 140, Frame 606)
    Paul Dieterich
  - Fund for Public Schools - #94-140, 1994 (Reel 140, Frame 747)
    Linda Frank
  - Fund for the City of New York - #11154, 1988 (Reel 140, Frame 938)
    Gregory Farrell
  - Fund for the City of New York - #9011, 1989 (Reel 140, Frame 1039)
  - Fund for the City of New York - #90-39, 1990 (Reel 141, Frame 1)
  - Fund for the City of New York - #92-19, 1991 (Reel 141, Frame 66)
    Marylinn Holobean
  - Fund for the City of New York - #9465, 1994 (Reel 141, Frame 189)
    Mary McCormick
  - Fund for the City of New York - #96023, 1995 (Reel 141, Frame 264)
  - Fund for the City of New York - #96911, 1996 (Reel 141, Frame 397)
  - Fund for the City of New York - #990259, 1999 (Reel 141, Frame 528)
  - Gay Men's Health Crisis - #95-62, 1995 (Reel 141, Frame 609)
    David Nimmons
  - GBSM, Inc. - #20010116, Tabs 1-4 (Reel 141, Frame 952)
    Robert Simon
  - GBSM, Inc. - #20010116, Tabs 5-10 (Reel 142, Frame 1)
  - George Washington University - #20000224, 2001 (Reel 142, Frame 115)
    Brian Biles
  - George Washington University - #92-36, 2000 (Reel 142, Frame 429)
    Richard Merritt
  - George Washington University - #92-77, 1991 (Reel 142, Frame 1057)
    Judith Jones
  - George Washington University - #93-33, 1992 (Reel 143, Frame 1)
    Peter Budetti
  - George Washington University - #93-34, 1993 (Reel 143, Frame 156)
  - George Washington University - #94-59, 1993 (Reel 143, Frame 415)
  - George Washington University - #94-61, 1994 (Reel 144, Frame 1)
  - George Washington University - #95881, 1994 (Reel 144, Frame 540)
    Deborah Lamm
  - George Washington University - #980772, 1995 (Reel 144, Frame 630)
    Sara Rosenbaum
  - George Washington University - #990566, 1998 (Reel 144, Frame 1024)
  - George Washington University - #9961, 1999 (Reel 145, Frame 1)
    Judith Miller Jones
  - George Washington University Center for Health Policy Research - #96175, 1999 (Reel 145, Frame 663)
    Ann Zuvekas
  - Georgetown University - #10160, 1996 (Reel 146, Frame 1)
    Judith Feder
  - Georgetown University - #10315, 1987 (Reel 146, Frame 524)
  - Georgetown University - #94-73, 1988 (Reel 146, Frame 838)
    Victor Cohn
  - Georgetown University - #95450, Tabs 1-2, 1994 (Reel 146, Frame 914)
    James Reuter
  - Georgetown University - #95450, Tabs 3-10, 1994 (Reel 147, Frame 1)
  - Georgetown University - #95-55, 1995 (Reel 147, Frame 307)
    Warren Reich
  - Georgetown University - #96962, 1995 (Reel 147, Frame 406)
    Harriet Komisar
  - Georgetown University - #970273, 1996 (Reel 147, Frame 783)
  - Georgetown University - #980205, 1997 (Reel 148, Frame 1)
  - Georgetown University - #980441, Tabs 1-3, 1998 (Reel 148, Frame 718)
  - Georgetown University - #980441, Tabs 4-10, 1998 (Reel 149, Frame 1)
  - Georgetown University - #980739, 1998 (Reel 149, Frame 134)
    Marian Gornick
  - Georgetown University Medical Center - #96959, 1998 (Reel 149, Frame 339)
  - Georgetown University Medical Center - #96963, Tabs 1-3, 1996 (Reel 149, Frame 803)
    Darryl Gaskin
  - Georgetown University Medical Center - #96963, Tabs 4-10, 1996 (Reel 150, Frame 1)
  - Georgetown University Medical Center - #970953, 1996 (Reel 150, Frame 174)
  - Georgetown University Medical Center - #980769, 1997 (Reel 151, Frame 1)
  - Georgetown University School of Medicine - #94-56, 1998 (Reel 151, Frame 695)
    Jack Hadley
  - Georgetown University School of Medicine - #96174, 1993 (Reel 152, Frame 1)
  - Gerontological Society of America - #990437, 1995 (Reel 152, Frame 203)
    Robert Friedland
  - Gerontological Society of America - #990907, 1999 (Reel 152, Frame 423)
  - Gift of Life Foundation - #20000414, 1999 (Reel 152, Frame 531)
    Maria Lopes
  - Giraffe Project - #93-50, 2000 (Reel 152, Frame 699)
    Jean Gaznier
  - Global Strategy Group, Inc. - #980519, 1993 (Reel 153, Frame 1)
    Peter Feld
  - Global Strategy Group, Inc. - #990199, 1998 (Reel 153, Frame 258)
  - Governor's Highway Safety Bureau of the Commonwealth of Massachusetts - #91-84, 1999 (Reel 154, Frame 1)
    Thomas McGovern
  - Governor's Highway Safety Bureau of the Commonwealth of Massachusetts - #92-18, 1991 (Reel 154, Frame 476)
  - Governor's Highway Safety Bureau of the Commonwealth of Massachusetts - #93-05, Tabs 1-9, 1992 (Reel 154, Frame 726)
  - Governor's Highway Safety Bureau of the Commonwealth of Massachusetts - #93-05, Tab 10, 1992 (Reel 155, Frame 1)
  - Grantmakers for Children, Youth and Families - #96649, 1993 (Reel 155, Frame 357)
    Mary Bogle
  - Grantmakers for Children, Youth and Families - #970641, 1996 (Reel 155, Frame 602)
  - Grantmakers in Aging, Inc. - #20040091, 1997 (Reel 155, Frame 791)
    Carol Farquhar
  - Grantmakers in Health - #11165, 2003 (Reel 155, Frame 875)
    Catherine McDermott
  - Grantmakers in Health - #20020130, 1989 (Reel 155, Frame 978)
    Anne Schwartz
  - Grantmakers in Health - #9032, 2002 (Reel 156, Frame 1)
  - Grantmakers in Health - #90-50, 1989 (Reel 156, Frame 499)
  - Grantmakers in Health - #91-73, 1990 (Reel 156, Frame 610)
  - Grantmakers in Health - #92-56, 1991 (Reel 157, Frame 1)
  - Grantmakers in Health - #93-62, 1992 (Reel 157, Frame 68)
  - Grantmakers in Health - #94-107, 1993 (Reel 157, Frame 200)
  - Grantmakers in Health - #94-97, 1994 (Reel 157, Frame 295)
  - Grantmakers in Health - #95-86, 1994 (Reel 157, Frame 335)
  - Grantmakers in Health - #96641, 1995 (Reel 157, Frame 390)
  - Grantmakers in Health - #96644, 1996 (Reel 157, Frame 556)
  - Grantmakers in Health - #970638, 1996 (Reel 157, Frame 598)
  - Grantmakers in Health - #980722, 1997 (Reel 157, Frame 671)
    Lauren LeRoy
  - Greater New York Hospital Foundation - #20000758, 1998 (Reel 157, Frame 948)
    Rima Cohen
  - Greater Philadelphia Urban Affairs Coalition - #91-10, 2000 (Reel 157, Frame 1022)
    P. Turner Bunyon
  - Greater Philadelphia Urban Affairs Coalition - #92-40, 1990 (Reel 158, Frame 1)
  - Greater Philadelphia Urban Affairs Coalition - #93-42, 1991 (Reel 158, Frame 444)
    Marciene Mattleman
  - Greater Philadelphia Urban Affairs Coalition - #94-64, Tabs 1-4, 1992 (Reel 158, Frame 753)
  - Greater Philadelphia Urban Affairs Coalition - #94-64, Tabs 5-10, 1992 (Reel 159, Frame 1)
  - Greater Philadelphia Urban Affairs Coalition - #95-39, 1993 (Reel 159, Frame 77)
  - Greater Philadelphia Urban Affairs Coalition - #96147, 1994 (Reel 159, Frame 464)
  - Greater Philadelphia Urban Affairs Coalition - #971050, 1995 (Reel 159, Frame 1095)
  - Greater Southeast Healthcare System - #92-62, 1996 (Reel 160, Frame 1)
    Dalton Tong
  - Greater Southeast Healthcare System - #93-04, 1991 (Reel 160, Frame 45)
    Jo Ann Kurtz
  - Greater Southeast Healthcare System - #93-84, 1992 (Reel 160, Frame 525)
    Thomas Chapman
  - Greater Southeast Healthcare System - #94-80, 1993 (Reel 160, Frame 957)
  - Greater Southeast Healthcare System - #95422, 1994 (Reel 161, Frame 1)
  - Greater Southeast Healthcare System - #96622, 1995 (Reel 161, Frame 852)
  - Greater Southeast Healthcare System - #970646, 1996 (Reel 162, Frame 1)
  - Greenbelt Conservancy, Inc. - #20000087, 1997 (Reel 162, Frame 443)
    Edward Toth
  - Hahnemann University Hospital - #94-37, 1999 (Reel 162, Frame 521)
    Iqbal Paroo
  - Harlem Interfaith Counseling Service - #92-29, 1993 (Reel 162, Frame 708)
    Doris Dennard
  - Harlem Interfaith Counseling Service - #94-132, 1991 (Reel 163, Frame 1)
  - Harvard Community Health Plan - #10236, 1994 (Reel 163, Frame 83)
    Donald M. Berwick
  - Harvard Community Health Plan - #10823, 1990 (Reel 163, Frame 329)
    Gordon Moore
  - Harvard Medical School - #20000218, 1988 (Reel 163, Frame 543)
    Paul Cleary
  - Harvard Medical School - #10842, 1999 (Reel 164, Frame 1)
    S. James Adelstein
  - Harvard Medical School - #90-82, 1989 (Reel 164, Frame 94)
    Edward Kravitz
  - Harvard Medical School - #92-11, 1990 (Reel 164, Frame 250)
  - Harvard Medical School - #94-127, 1991 (Reel 164, Frame 516)
    Edward Guadagnoli
  - Harvard Medical School - #95420, 1994 (Reel 165, Frame 1)
    Joan Reede
  - Harvard Medical School - #95-45, 1995 (Reel 165, Frame 368)
    Pamela Barron
  - Harvard Medical School - #95521, 1995 (Reel 166, Frame 1)
    Ezekiel Emanuel
  - Harvard Medical School - #95-77, 1995 (Reel 166, Frame 937)
    Daniel Tosteson
  - Harvard Medical School - #96022, 1995 (Reel 166, Frame 1085)
    Arnold Epstein
  - Harvard Medical School - #96186, Tabs 1-3, 1996 (Reel 167, Frame 1)
  - Harvard Medical School - #96186, Tab 3 (continued), 1996 (Reel 168, Frame 1)
  - Harvard Medical School - #96186, Tabs 4-10, 1996 (Reel 169, Frame 1)
  - Harvard Medical School - #96914, 1996 (Reel 169, Frame 790)
    Gerald Koocher
  - Harvard Medical School - #96952, 1996 (Reel 169, Frame 1128)
    Joseph Newhouse
  - Harvard Medical School - #970268, Tabs 1-7, 1996 (Reel 170, Frame 1)
  - Harvard Medical School - #970268, Tabs 8-10, 1996 (Reel 171, Frame 1)
  - Harvard Medical School - #970940, 1997 (Reel 171, Frame 306)
  - Harvard Medical School - #9723, 1997 (Reel 171, Frame 881)
  - Harvard Medical School - #980414, 1997 (Reel 172, Frame 1)
    Michael Rosenblatt
  - Harvard Medical School - #980440, 1998 (Reel 172, Frame 144)
  - Harvard Medical School - #980774, Tabs 1-3, 1998 (Reel 172, Frame 529)
  - Harvard Medical School - #980774, Tabs 4-10, 1998 (Reel 173, Frame 1)
  - Harvard Medical School - #980909, 1998 (Reel 173, Frame 457)
    Leon Eisenberg
  - Harvard Medical School, Division of Health Policy Education and Research - #9871, 1998 (Reel 173, Frame 511)
  - Harvard Pilgrim Health Care - #980666, 1998 (Reel 173, Frame 651)
  - Harvard School of Public Health - #11125, Tabs 1-4, 1998 (Reel 173, Frame 761)
    M. Roberts
  - Harvard School of Public Health - #11125, Tabs 5-10, 1998 (Reel 174, Frame 1)
  - Harvard School of Public Health - #5624, 1991 (Reel 174, Frame 701)
    Howard H. Hiatt
  - Harvard School of Public Health - #9727/90-37 - File 1, Tabs 1-5, 1987 (Reel 174, Frame 731)
    Jay Winsten
  - Harvard School of Public Health - #9727/90-37 - File 1, Tabs 6-10, 1987 (Reel 175, Frame 1)
  - Harvard School of Public Health - #9727/90-37 - File 2, Tabs 1-5, 1987 (Reel 175, Frame 99)
  - Harvard School of Public Health - #9727/90-37 - File 2, Tab 5 (continued), 1987 (Reel 176, Frame 1)
  - Harvard School of Public Health - #90-57, 1987 (Reel 176, Frame 719)
    Frank Mosteller
  - Harvard School of Public Health - #91-52, 1990 (Reel 176, Frame 933)
    Robert Blendon
  - Harvard School of Public Health - #91-62, 1990 (Reel 176, Frame 1077)
    Penny Feldman
  - Harvard School of Public Health - #91-86, 1990 (Reel 177, Frame 1)
    Diana C. Walsh
  - Harvard School of Public Health - #92-67, 1991 (Reel 177, Frame 417)
  - Harvard School of Public Health - #92-71, 1992 (Reel 177, Frame 739)
  - Harvard School of Public Health - #93-19, Tabs 1-2, 1992 (Reel 177, Frame 920)
  - Harvard School of Public Health - #93-19, Tabs 3-10, 1992 (Reel 178, Frame 1)
  - Harvard School of Public Health - #93-76, 1992 (Reel 178, Frame 291)
  - Harvard School of Public Health - #94-12, 1993 (Reel 178, Frame 661)
    Nancy Kane
  - Harvard School of Public Health - #96058, 1994 (Reel 178, Frame 914)
    Katherine Swartz
  - Harvard School of Public Health - #970622, 1995 (Reel 178, Frame 1004)
  - Harvard School of Public Health - #97064, 1996 (Reel 179, Frame 1)
    S. Jody Heymann
  - Harvard School of Public Health - #970645, 1996 (Reel 179, Frame 155)
    Jack Needleman
  - Harvard School of Public Health - #970926, 1997 (Reel 180, Frame 1)
  - Harvard School of Public Health - #980753, 1997 (Reel 180, Frame 414)
    Eric Schneider
  - Harvard School of Public Health - #980827, Tabs 1-2, 1997 (Reel 180, Frame 724)
    Robert Blendon & Karen Donelan
  - Harvard School of Public Health - #980827, Tabs 3-10, 1997 (Reel 181, Frame 1)
  - Harvard School of Public Health - #980868, 1997 (Reel 181, Frame 225)
    Karen Donelan
  - Harvard School of Public Health - #9830, 1998 (Reel 181, Frame 328)
    Jay Winston